{
    "id": "2e205ad39e964b64922bc18bee99456e",
    "title": "Adjectives or present participles",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a352adbb148f45cca278b19aa915a38e",
            "title": "Adjective Or Present Participle",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Interesting though it was, we didnâ€™t enjoy the concert much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Interesting is an adjective",
                        "Interesting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was raining when I got home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Raining is an adjective",
                        "Raining is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I love the noise of falling rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Falling is an adjective",
                        "Falling is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is a pressing problem.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Pressing is an adjective",
                        "Pressing is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was writing a letter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Writing is an adjective",
                        "Writing is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The lecture was very interesting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Interesting is an adjective",
                        "Interesting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is an interesting writer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Interesting is an adjective",
                        "Interesting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The woodcutter was felling trees.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Felling is an adjective",
                        "Felling is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news was exciting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Exciting is an adjective",
                        "Exciting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was working on that report when she called.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Working is an adjective",
                        "Working is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}